Guide to the Ohio State University, Office of the President (Harold Leroy Enarson) Records, 1940s-2002 RG.3.J
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
- Processed, 1971-1981; 54.0 Cubic feet; (45) cartons
  - Correspondence: Engagements, 1978-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0016, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Introduction, 1972-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0016, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Personal, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0016, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Personal, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0016, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Personal, 1977-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0016, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Personal, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0016, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Recommendations, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0016, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Recommendations, 1976-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0016, Folder 13)
  - Council on International Scientific and Technical Cooperation: Correspondence, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0016, Folder 14)
  - Council of Ten: ABC Matters (American Broadcasting Network): Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0016, Folder 15)
  - Council of Ten: College Football Association: Correspondence, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0016, Folder 16)
  - Council of Ten: Minutes and Reports (Incl. Correspondence), 1973-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0016, Folder 17)
  - Council of Ten: Minutes and Reports (Incl. Correspondence), 1977-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0016, Folder 18)
  - Crawford, Edwin McNeill: Correspondence, 1974-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0016, Folder 19)
  - Day Care Center, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 1)
  - Deans: Council of, 1977-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 2)
  - Deans: Council of: Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 3)
  - Deans: Council of: Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 4)
  - Deans: Council of: Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 5)
  - Deans: Council of: Report: Enrollment Management in the 80's, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 6)
  - Deans: Council of: Report: Major Issues Facing Universities in Affirmative Action and Equal Pay, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 7)
  - Deans: Council of: Report: Recommendation on Improved Quarter-End Validation Procedures, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 8)
  - Dentistry: College of: Accreditation, 1974-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 9)
  - Dentistry: College of: Complaints, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 10)
  - Dentistry: College of: Correspondence, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 11)
  - Dentistry: College of: Minority Recruitment, 1974-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 12)
  - Dentistry: College of: Selection of a New Dean, 1974-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 13)
  - Development Fund: Annual Giving Analysis and Development Plan, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 14)
  - Development Fund: Board of Directors: Discretionary Fund, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 15)
  - Development Fund: Correspondence, 1974-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 16)
  - Development Fund: Davis Committee: Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 17)
  - Development Fund: External Study (Phase II), 1977 September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 18)
  - Development Fund: Financial Statement Reports, 1974-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 19)
  - Development Fund: Gifts and Fellowships: Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 20)
  - Development Fund: Gifts and Fellowships: Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 21)
  - Development Fund: Gifts and Fellowships: Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 22)
  - Development Fund: Internal Audit, 1977 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 23)
  - Development Fund: OSU Program for a Better University, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 24)
  - Development Fund: Search Committee: Correspondence, 1974-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 25)
  - Dinnan Case: Concerning the Confidentiality of Personnel Evaluations, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 26)
  - Distinguished Service Awards: Correspondence and Deliberation, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 27)
  - Don Scott Field: Correspondence, 1972-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 28)
  - Don Scott Field: Master Plan Study: Executive Summary, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 29)
  - Don Scott Field: Report: Aircraft Accident PA-28 Cherokee N-26 OSU, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 30)
  - Don Scott Field: Study of Proposed Fee Increases, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 31)
  - Education: College of: Black Education Program, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 32)
  - Education: College of: Correspondence, 1972-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0017, Folder 33)
  - Education: College of: Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 1)
  - Education: College of: Dean Search, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 2)
  - Educational Services: Vice-President for: Calendar Year Progress Report, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 3)
  - Educational Services: Vice-President for: Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 4)
  - Educational Services: Vice-President for: Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 5)
  - Educational Services: Vice-President for: Educational Data, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 6)
  - Educational Services: Vice-President for: Expenditure and Budget Requests, 1973-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 7)
  - Educational Services: Vice-President for: Funding by the Board of Regents, 1973-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 8)
  - Educational Services: Vice-President for: Learning Resources Center, 1974-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 9)
  - Educational Services: Vice-President for: Matters of Public Record, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 10)
  - Educational Services: Vice-President for: Monthly Reports, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 11)
  - Educational Services: Vice-President for: Monthly Reports, 1975-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 12)
  - Educational Services: Vice-President for: Monthly Reports, 1978-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 13)
  - Educational Services: Vice-President for: Ohio Appalachian Community Service Network, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 14)
  - Educational Services: Vice-President for: Report of the Study of Learning Resources at OSU, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 15)
  - Educational Services: Vice-President for: Technical and Business Services Program, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 16)
  - Educational Services: Vice-President for: Telecommunications in Teaching, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 17)
  - Educational Services: Vice-President for: WOSU, 1973-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 18)
  - Educational Services: Vice-President for: Promotion Tenure: Employee Relations: See Collective Bargaining, 1974-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 19)
  - Enarson, Harold L.: Biographical Notes, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 20)
  - "The Enarson Years": WOSU Video and Audio-Tape, 1981 June 8 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 21)
  - Energy: Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 22)
  - Energy: Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 23)
  - Energy Extension Service: Proposal to Plan, Develop, and Operate, 1977 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 24)
  - Energy Related Research Programs: An Inventory, 1977 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 25)
  - Engineering: College of: Correspondence, 1972-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 26)
  - Engineering: College of: Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 27)
  - Engineering: College of: Mechanical Engineering: Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 28)
  - Engineering: College of: Transportation Research Center, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 29)
  - Enrollment: Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 30)
  - Enrollment: Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 31)
  - Enrollment: Enrollment of "Older" Students in Credit, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 32)
  - Enrollment: Enrollment Plans, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 33)
  - Enrollment: Headcounts and Credit Hours of Instruction, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 34)
  - Enrollment: Report: Enrollment Management in the 80's, undated (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 35)
  - Enrollment: Report: Enrollment Patterns: Columbus Campus, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 36)
  - Enrollment: Report: Enrollment Related Issues, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0018, Folder 37)
  - Enrollment Statistics, 1972-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 1)
  - Enrollment Statistics, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 2)
  - Enrollment Statistics, 1978-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 3)
  - Enrollment Trends: Memos, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 4)
  - Executive Vice-President: Moulton, Edward and Richard Zimmerman: Correspondence, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Advisory Committee, 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Club, 1972-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Salary Analysis of Selected Big Ten Universities, 1972-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 8)
  - Family Educational Rights and Privacy, 1972-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 9)
  - Fawcett Center for Tomorrow: Correspondence, 1972-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 10)
  - Fawcett Center for Tomorrow: Evaluation of the Organization and Operation, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 11)
  - Fawcett Center for Tomorrow: Policies, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 12)
  - Fawcett Center for Tomorrow: Third Floor Funding, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 13)
  - Federal Legislation: Committee on: Reports, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 14)
  - Federally Mandated Social Programs: Costs to Colleges and Universities of Implementing: Report, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 15)
  - Fee Revenues: Memos, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 16)
  - Fees: Correspondence, 1974-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 17)
  - Finance and Investment Committee, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 18)
  - Finance and Treasurer, 1972-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 19)
  - Finance and Treasurer, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 20)
  - Fire Drills and Fire Reports, 1972-1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 21)
  - Football: Air Traffic in Stadium Area, 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 22)
  - Football: Correspondence, 1972-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 23)
  - Football: Fiesta Bowl, 1980 December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 24)
  - Football: Gator Bowl, 1978 December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 25)
  - Football: Head Coach: Search, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 26)
  - Football: Ohio Shrine Bowl, 1972 August (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 27)
  - Football: Orange Bowl, 1976 November-1977 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 28)
  - Football: Post-Michigan Game Plans, 1972-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 29)
  - Football: President's Remarks at Football Appreciation Banquet, 1980 November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 30)
  - Football: Rose Bowl, 1973 June-1980 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 31)
  - Football: Scholarships, 1976-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 32)
  - Football: Sugar Bowl, 1977 November-1978 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 33)
  - Football: Tickets, 1972-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 34)
  - Football: Woody Hayes, 1974-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 35)
  - Foundations, 1972-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 36)
  - Foundations, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 37)
  - Fraternities and Sororities, 1972-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 38)
  - Fulbright Awards, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0019, Folder 39)
  - Gifts: Correspondence, 1972-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 1)
  - Gilligan: "Ohio Plan": Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 2)
  - Gilligan: "Ohio Plan": Governor's Budget, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 3)
  - Gilligan: "Ohio Plan": Student Advisory Board to the Governor, 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 4)
  - Graduate Council: Guidelines Related to Graduate Associates, 1969 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Education: Task Force on, 1975 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 6)
  - Graduate School: Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 7)
  - Graduate School: Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 8)
  - Graduate School: Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 9)
  - Graduate School: Dean Search, 1974 July-September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 10)
  - Graduate School: Enrollment Figures, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 11)
  - Graduate Students: Council of: Administration-Student Retreat, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 12)
  - Graduate Students: Council of: Correspondence, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 13)
  - Graduate Students: Human Subject Program Guidelines, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 14)
  - Graduate Students: Council of: Report, 1977-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 15)
  - Graduate Students: Foreign: Statistics, 1978-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 16)
  - Grants: Health, Education and Welfare, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 17)
  - Grants: Health, Education and Welfare, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 18)
  - Grants: Health, Education and Welfare, 1977-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 19)
  - Grants: Unrestricted, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 20)
  - Grants and Contract Agreements: Between the OSU and the State of Ohio, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 21)
  - Greek Affairs: Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 22)
  - Greek Affairs: Education Fund, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 23)
  - Green, David: Case of Dismissal, 1968-1969 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 24)
    Confidential
  - Green, David: Case of Dismissal, 1971-1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 25)
  - Griffith Foundation: Correspondence and Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 26)
  - Griffith Foundation: Correspondence and Minutes, 1975-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 27)
  - Griffith Foundation: Correspondence and Minutes, 1978-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 28)
  - Griffith Foundation: International Insurance Seminar: Board of Directors: Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0020, Folder 29)
  - Hayes, Wayne Woodrow "Woody": Correspondence: Gator Bowl, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 1)
  - Hayes, Wayne Woodrow "Woody": Correspondence: Gator Bowl, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 2)
  - Hayes, Wayne Woodrow "Woody": Correspondence Concerning, 1974-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 3)
  - Hayes, Wayne Woodrow "Woody": Cameraman Issue, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 4)
  - Hayes, Wayne Woodrow "Woody": Rose Bowl Photographer Incident, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 5)
  - Hayes, Wayne Woodrow "Woody": Rose Bowl Photographer Incident: Newsclippings, 1973-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 6)
  - Hayes, Wayne Woodrow "Woody": Rose Bowl Photographer Incident: Resignation/Retirement, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 7)
  - HEW: Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 8)
  - HEW: Correspondence: Health Science Library: See Medical Affairs: Vice President for, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 9)
  - Health Services: Correspondence, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 10)
  - Health Services: Search for Vice-President, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 11)
  - Health Services: Search for Vice-President, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 12)
  - Hill, George E.: Football Contract Negotiations, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 13)
  - Hill, George E.: NCAA: Football Recruitment Allegations, 1977-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 14)
  - Home Economics: School of: Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 15)
  - Honorary Degrees: Acceptance and Awarding, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 16)
  - Honorary Degrees: Approval, 1975-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 17)
  - Honorary Degrees: Approval, 1978-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 18)
  - Honorary Degrees: Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 19)
  - Honorary Degrees: Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 20)
  - Honorary Degrees: Criteria for Selection, 1973-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 21)
  - Honorary Degrees: Nomination, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 22)
  - Honorary Degrees: Nomination, 1976-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 23)
  - Honorary Degrees: Nomination, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 24)
  - Hospital Board: Correspondence, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 25)
  - Hospital Board: Medical Practice Plan, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 26)
  - Hospital Board: Paper: Governance of the University Hospitals, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 27)
  - Housing, Mortgage and Rehabilitation Loan Program: Proposal, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 28)
  - Humanities: College of: Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 29)
  - Humanities: College of: Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 30)
  - Humanities: College of: Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 31)
  - Humanities: College of: Russian Language and Training, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 32)
  - Humanities: College of: Search Committee: Dean of Humanities, 1977-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 33)
  - Humanities: College of: Survey: East European and Russian Language Institutes and Courses Offered in the United States, Canada, and Europe, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0021, Folder 34)
  - Immigration: Odita, Dr. Emmanuel O., 1970-1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 1)
  - Inauguration: Correspondence, 1972 July-December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 2)
  - Inauguration: Greetings of Brigham Young University, 1973 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 3)
  - Inauguration: Greetings of California State College, 1973 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 4)
  - Inauguration: Greetings of Colleges (1 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 5)
  - Inauguration: Greetings of Colleges (2 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 6)
  - Inauguration: Greetings of Northern Arizona University, 1972 December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 7)
  - Inauguration: Greetings of Spalding College, 1972 December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 8)
  - Inauguration: Greetings of Springfield College, 1973 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 9)
  - Inauguration: Greetings of Trinity University, 1973 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 10)
  - Inauguration: Greetings of Wayne State, 1973 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 11)
  - Income Contingent Loan Plans: Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 12)
  - Income Contingent Loan Plans: Proposal to Establish an Ohio Direct Student Loan Program, 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 13)
  - India Trip: Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 14)
  - Institute of Ecology: Correspondence, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 15)
  - Institute on International Education: Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 16)
  - Instruction and Research Computer Center: Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 17)
  - Instruction and Research Computer Center: Report: College Interviews on Computing Service, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 18)
  - Instruction and Research Computer Center: Report: 370 Model 165 Utilization Summary, 1973 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 19)
  - Insurance Reports, 1973-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 20)
  - Intercollegiate Conference: Conference, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 21)
  - Intercollegiate Conference: Memorandums, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 22)
  - Intercollegiate Conference: Memorandums, 1976-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 23)
  - Intercollegiate Conference: Office of Commissioner of Athletics: Report of Sources of Funds and Expenditures for Financial Assistance, 1971-1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 24)
  - Intercollegiate Conference: Report on Women's Intercollegiate Athletics, 1974-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 25)
  - International Association of Universities: Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 26)
  - International Association of Universities Report: Academic Freedom and Tenure, 1971 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 27)
  - International Programs: Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 28)
  - International Programs: Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 29)
  - International Programs: Correspondence, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 30)
  - International Programs: Correspondence, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 31)
  - International Programs: Working Paper: Proposed Program of Activities, 1975 July (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 32)
  - International Students: Correspondence, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0022, Folder 33)
  - Inter-University Council (of Ohio), 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 1)
  - Inter-University Council (of Ohio): Committee to Draft Legislations to Purchase Liability Insurance, 1974 November 8 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 2)
  - Inter-University Council (of Ohio): Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 3)
  - Inter-University Council (of Ohio): Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 4)
  - Inter-University Council (of Ohio): Fiscal Officers Meetings: Minutes, 1977-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 5)
  - Inter-University Council (of Ohio): Minutes, 1973-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 6)
  - Inter-University Council (of Ohio): Nursing Education and Nursing Registration: Proposed Rule Changes, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 7)
  - Inter-University Council (of Ohio): Presidents' Meeting with Chancellor: Minutes, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 8)
  - Inter-University Council (of Ohio): Quarterly Trustees' Meeting: Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 9)
  - Inter-University Council (of Ohio): Student Affairs Committee: Minutes, 1977-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 10)
  - Journal of Higher Education, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 11)
  - Journalism: School of: Borden Boycott Dispute, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 12)
  - Journalism: School of: Bunge, Walter: Director, 1978 March-1980 November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 13)
  - Journalism: School of: Caniff, Milton: Dedication of Research Room, 1978 October-1979 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 14)
  - Journalism: School of: Correspondence: General, 1973 September-1980 November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 15)
  - Journalism: School of: Correspondence: Lantern Staff, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 16)
  - Journalism: School of: Gubernational Race Comments by John D. Jacob to R.R. Theis, 1979 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 17)
  - Journalism: School of: Hall, William, 1973-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 18)
  - Journalism: School of: Harless, James D. (Possible Legal Action), 1980 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 19)
  - Journalism: School of: Nuessle/Carter Alcoholism Photo Dispute, 1975 March-April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 20)
  - Journalism: School of: Overload Farm Buffet Luncheon, 1974 September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 21)
  - Journalism: School of: 60th Anniversary Celebration and New Building Dedication, 1974 September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 22)
  - Journalism: School of: Status Report, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 23)
  - Kellogg Foundation: Conference on Education for Health Administrations, 1976 July 16-18 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 24)
  - Journalism: School of: Correspondence, 1975 July-1976 November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 25)
  - Kellogg Foundation: Task Force on Centers for Advanced Study in Health Administration, 1975 November-1976 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 26)
  - Kindred, Susan T. (Director of Affirmative Action): Promotion: Lake Erie Area Research: See Center for Lake Erie Area Research, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 27)
  - Law: College of: Correspondence, 1972-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 28)
  - Law: College of: Search for Dean, 1974-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 29)
  - Legal Cases: Agora Columbus vs. OSU Liquor License, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 30)
  - Legal Cases: Alexander, Lloyd T. vs. OSU and State of Ohio, 1975-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 31)
  - Legal Cases: Allen, Larry vs. Board of Trustees, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 32)
  - Legal Cases: Alls, Ethel vs. Madison H. Scott, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 33)